https://www.powertoolsalesuk.com/privacy-policy-2/

Privacy Policy - Power Tool Sales
02380 315 316 Free Delivery On Orders Over £95* Skip to navigation
Skip to content
Visit Our Store  My account
Products searchSearch
MenuMENUMENUShop Air ToolsAir Cutting ToolsHigh Speed CutterNibblersSawsAir Drills1/2" Drills3/8" Drills1/4" DrillsAir Grinders7" Angle Grinders5" Angle Grinders4 1/2" Angle Grinders4" Angle Grinders2" Angle GrindersAngle Die GrindersPencil GrindersStraight Die GrindersAir Hammers & ScalersHammersScalers & ChippersAir Impact Wrenches1" Impact Wrenches3/4" Impact Wrenches1/2" Impact Wrenches3/8" Impact Wrenches1/4" Impact WrenchesAir Ratchet Wrenches1/2" Ratchet Wrenches3/8" Ratchet Wrenches1/4" Ratchet WrenchesAir Sanders8" Sanders7" Sanders6" Sanders5" Sanders3" SandersBelt SandersDelta SandersSanding AccessoriesAir ScrewdriversDirect Clutch ScrewdriversImpact ScrewdriversRoller Clutch ScrewdriversShut Off Clutch ScrewdriversSlip Clutch ScrewdriversAir Speciality ToolsCaulking GunsEngraving PensFilesRivetersTyre BuffersAir Tool AccessoriesAdaptors & CouplingsAir HosesAnti-Whip TailsHAV TestLubricators & RegulatorsOther AccessoriesDust ExtractionATEX Approved Dust ExtractionMobile Dust ExtractionWorkshop EquipmentAir CompressorsAxle StandsHydraulic PressesJacksTorque WrenchesVehicle Jump PacksShop Electric ToolsIndustrial ToolsMag DrillsNibblersTappersCordless ToolsCordless DrillsCordless GrindersCordless Impact DriversCordless Impact WrenchesCordless NibblersCordless ShearsCordless TappersElectric DrillsElectric Hand DrillsElectric SandersRUPES Electric SandersMirka Electric SandersElectric GrindersElectric Die GrindersElectric Vertical GrindersFein Electric ToolsFein Multi ToolsFein Multi Tool AccessoriesOther Electric ToolsElectric Heat GunsElectric ScrewdriversElectric ShearsShop AutomotiveBody Shop
Dust Extraction, Polishing & Sanding
Vehicle Detailing
Compounds, Pads & Polishing
Vehicle Servicing
Air Lines, Tooling & Workshop Equipment
Tool Servicing & RepairsHAV TestingContact UsInfoAbout UsBrandsDelivery InformationReturns & RefundsTerms & Conditions
Products searchSearch
Cart£0.00Shop Air ToolsAir Cutting ToolsHigh Speed CutterNibblersSawsAir Drills1/2" Drills3/8" Drills1/4" DrillsAir Grinders7" Angle Grinders5" Angle Grinders4 1/2" Angle Grinders4" Angle Grinders2" Angle GrindersAngle Die GrindersPencil GrindersStraight Die GrindersAir Hammers & ScalersHammersScalers & ChippersAir Impact Wrenches1" Impact Wrenches3/4" Impact Wrenches1/2" Impact Wrenches3/8" Impact Wrenches1/4" Impact WrenchesAir Ratchet Wrenches1/2" Ratchet Wrenches3/8" Ratchet Wrenches1/4" Ratchet WrenchesAir Sanders8" Air Sanders7" Air Sanders6" Air Sanders5" Air Sanders3" Air SandersBelt SandersDelta SandersJitterbug SandersLong Bed SandersSanding AccessoriesAir ScrewdriversDirect Clutch ScrewdriversImpact ScrewdriversRoller Clutch ScrewdriversShut Off Clutch ScrewdriversSlip Clutch ScrewdriversAir Speciality ToolsCaulking GunsEngraving PensFilesRivetersTyre BuffersAir Tool AccessoriesAdaptors & CouplingsAir HosesAnti-Whip TailsHAV TestLubricators & RegulatorsOther AccessoriesDust ExtractionATEX Approved Dust ExtractionMobile Dust ExtractionWorkshop EquipmentAir CompressorsAxle StandsHydraulic PressesJacksTorque WrenchesVehicle Jump PacksShop Electric ToolsIndustrial ToolsMag DrillsNibblersTappersCordless ToolsCordless DrillsCordless GrindersCordless Impact DriversCordless Impact WrenchesCordless NibblersCordless ShearsCordless TappersElectric DrillsElectric Hand DrillsElectric SandersRUPES Electric SandersMirka Electric SandersElectric GrindersElectric Die GrindersElectric Vertical GrindersOther Electric ToolsElectric Heat GunsElectric ScrewdriversElectric ShearsElectric Tool AccessoriesShop AutomotiveVehicle DetailingRUPES Vehicle PolishersRUPES Backing PadsRUPES Polishing CompoundsRUPES Foam Polishing PadsRUPES Microfibre PadsRUPES Wool PadsAccessories & Misc ConsumablesRUPES SparesBody ShopVehicle ServicingTool Servicing & RepairsREMS Tool Servicing & CalibrationHand Arm Vibration TestingContact UsInfoAbout UsDelivery & Shipping InformationReturns & RefundsTerms & Conditions
£0.00 0 items
Home / Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how Power Tool Sales Ltd uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website.Power Tool Sales Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.What we collectWe may collect the following information:• name and job title• contact information including email address• demographic information such as address• information relevant to customer surveys and/or offersWhat we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:• Internal record keeping.• We may use the information to improve our products and services.• We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.• From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.How we use cookiesA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites. You should exercise caution and read the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Controlling your personal informationIf you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or sending us a message via the Contact Form.We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
Recent Posts
What pads & accessories are compatible with the RUPES iBrid Nano?
28 July 2020
RUPES iBrid Nano Sander with Q-Mag Technology
20 February 2020Secure Payments
Powered By
ISO 9001 CertifiedInformationAbout UsContact UsTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyDelivery InformationReturns & Refunds
© Power Tool Sales 2020
Privacy PolicyBuilt with Storefront & WooCommerce.
